force has always been a big passion and
motivation for me and when Sports comes
in the form of a social inclusion which
integrates the society I think that's
one of the biggest motivators for me to
join enjoy volunteering in the community
and getting to know people around
Singapore and help out it's a good fun
experience since very rewarding I really
really like joining events and I like to
see people and foes alike help me first
of all so the first thing I when I see
like the email on this event I
definitely want to join this thing it's
a great fun they are very high-energy
they all the athletes
I joined playing badminton and I was
keeping the track of the score in the
badminton game oh well it has been a lot
of fun being up here this morning and
seeing the smiles across people their
spirits and how they have been
participating and how their hard work is
paying off so it's been a lot of fun to
be out here with all the teammates and
spending the day out here I really enjoy
myself here you know
seeing other kids having fun and
everything I love it the sports and
social inclusion delivers the right
message and it's something that we
believe in changing the way people feel
about insurance it's also about how
people feel about how sports can change
lives so I think it's a very combined
and unified message that both the teams
have so it's wonderful I think it's
awesome
I walk the Special Olympics in the u.s.
a few times and I really enjoyed it I
really enjoy getting to know the
athletes and spend time with them so I'm
very glad I'm WG partner and after the
Special Olympics
so they say sports brings people
together and there is no greater
evidence of that ban today it's just
wonderful to see so many athletes so
many partners to members all come
together and and celebrate the joy of
sports and I would just invite you and I
urge you to join us when we do it again
the next time because today has been
just wonderful and a big thank you and
congratulations to all the athletes who
joined us and a big thank you to all the
staff who volunteer to make this a big
big success so again see you next time